<resources>
    <string name="app_name">The Leonhard-Shmishek Test</string>
    <string name="test_name">The Leonhard-Shmishek Test</string>
    <string name="description">The personality questionnaire, which is designed to diagnose the type of character accentuation, is the implementation of a typological
        approach to its study.</string>
    <string name="create_account"><u>I want to create an account</u></string>
    <string name="time_test">9 minutes</string>
    <string name="vopros_kol">88 questions</string>
    <string name="quest">Do you want to take the test?</string>
    <string name="personal">Profile</string>
    <string name="test">Test</string>
    <string name="email"> Email</string>
    <string name="password"> Password</string>
    <string name="autorization">Authorization</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="registration">Registration</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="noAccount">I don\'t have an account</string>
    <string name="reset_password">I forgot my password</string>
    <string name="gender_check">Gender</string>
    <string name="register">Create an account</string>
    <string name="infoAccount">What is an account for?</string>
    <string name="my_personal">My profile</string>
    <string name="edit_personal">Edit profile</string>
    <string name="result">View statistics</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="yes"> Yes </string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="statistic">Statistic</string>
    <string name="test_desc_header">Test Description</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="diagram_result">Results chart</string>
    <string name="go_test">Start the test</string>

    <string name="delimiter">*****************************************</string>
    <string name="typesDescription">Description of psychotypes</string>
    <string name="demonstrative"> 1. Demonstrative type. It is characterized by an increased ability to repress, demonstrative behavior, liveliness, mobility, ease in
        establishing contacts. He is prone to fantasy, falsehood and pretense aimed at embellishing his person, adventurism, artistry, posturing. He is driven by the
        desire for leadership, the need for recognition, the thirst for constant attention to his person, the thirst for power, praise; the prospect of being unnoticed
        burdens him. </string>
    <string name="stuck">2. The stuck type. He is characterized by moderate sociability, boredom, a penchant for moralizing, taciturnity. Often suffers from imaginary
        injustice towards him. In this regard, he is wary and distrustful of people, sensitive to insults and upsets, vulnerable, suspicious, vindictive, experiences
        what happened for a long time, is not able to "easily move away" from insults. </string>
    <string name="pedantic">3. Pedantic type. It is characterized by rigidity, inertia of mental processes, heaviness on the rise, long experience of traumatic events.
        He rarely enters into conflicts, acting as a passive rather than an active party. At the same time, it reacts very strongly to any manifestation of disorder.
        In the service, he behaves like a bureaucrat, making many formal demands to others.</string>
    <string name="excitable">4. Excitable type. Insufficient controllability, weakening of control over drives and impulses are combined in people of this type with
        the power of physiological drives. He is characterized by increased impulsivity, instinctiveness, rudeness, boredom, sullenness, anger, a tendency to rudeness
        and abuse, to friction and conflicts, in which he himself is an active, provoking party.</string>
    <string name="hyperthymic">5. Hyperthymic type. People of this type are distinguished by great mobility, sociability, talkativeness, expressive gestures, facial
        expressions, pantomimics, excessive independence, a tendency to mischief, lack of a sense of distance in relationships with others. They often spontaneously
        deviate from the original topic in conversation. They make a lot of noise everywhere, they love the companies of their peers, they strive to command them. They
        almost always have a very good mood, good health, high vitality, often blooming appearance, good appetite, healthy sleep, a tendency to gluttony and other joys of
        life.</string>
    <string name="disthymic">6. Dysthymic type. People of this type are distinguished by seriousness, even depression of mood, slowness, weakness of volitional efforts.
        They are characterized by a pessimistic attitude to the future, low self-esteem, as well as low contact, taciturnity in conversation, even taciturnity.</string>
    <string name="anxiouslyFearFull">7. An anxious type. People of this type are characterized by low contact, a minor mood, timidity, timidity, self-doubt. Children of
        the anxious type are often afraid of the dark, animals, afraid to be alone. They avoid noisy and lively peers, do not like excessively noisy games, feel a sense
        of shyness and shyness, they are hard going through tests, exams, checks. They often hesitate to answer in front of the class. They willingly submit to the
        guardianship of their elders, adult notations can cause them remorse, guilt, tears, despair.</string>
    <string name="emotionally">8. Cyclothymic type. It is characterized by a change of hyperthymic and dysthymic states. They are characterized by frequent periodic
        mood swings, as well as dependence on external events. Joyful events cause them pictures of hyperthymia: thirst for activity, increased talkativeness, leap of
        ideas; sad - depression, slowness of reactions and thinking, their manner of communication with people around them also often changes. In adolescence, two
        variants of cyclothymic accentuation can be found: typical and labile cycloids.</string>
    <string name="emotive">9. The exalted type. The bright feature of this type is the ability to admire, admire, and also - smiling, feeling of happiness, joy,
        enjoyment. These feelings can often arise in them for a reason that does not cause much uplift in others, they easily become delighted with joyful events and
        in complete despair – from sad ones. They are characterized by high contact, talkativeness, amorous.</string>
    <string name="cyclothymic">10. Emotive type. This type is related to the exalted, but its manifestations are not so violent. They are characterized by emotionality,
        sensitivity, anxiety, talkativeness, fearfulness, deep reactions in the field of subtle feelings. The most pronounced trait is humanity, empathy for other
        people or animals, responsiveness, soft-heartedness, joy in other people\'s successes. </string>
    <string name="birthday">Birthday</string>
    <string name="male">Male</string>
    <string name="female">Female</string>

    <string name="test_description">
        We offer you to take a character accentuation test, or a Schmishek questionnaire, and find out which types of accentuation are most pronounced in you.
        As the name of the test implies, the questionnaire was developed by Shmishek on the basis of the dominant character traits identified by Leonhard for a particular type.
        This accentuation test consists of 88 questions concerning 10 types of accentuations.
    </string>
    <string name="instruction">
        You will be offered statements concerning your character.
        Answer without hesitation for a long time, you can choose one of two answers: "yes" or "no", there are no other answers.
        You need to click on your answer, after which you will have a button to go to the next question
    </string>
    <string name="email_forgot_pass">Enter your email and we will send a new password to your email</string>
    <string name="send">Send a new password</string>
    <string name="edit_profile">Editing a profile</string>
    <string name="old_password">Old password</string>
    <string name="repeat_new_password">Repeat the new password</string>
    <string name="new_password">New password</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="repeat_password">Repeat password</string>
    <string name="incorrect">Invalid username or password</string>
    <string name="successfully">Authorization is successful</string>
    <string name="enter_email_password">Enter your email and password</string>
    <string name="length_password">The password must be longer than 8 characters</string>
    <string name="password_successfully">Password changed successfully</string>
    <string name="opassword_incorrect">The old password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="match_password">Passwords must match</string>
    <string name="opassword_and_npassword">Enter the old password and the new password 2 times</string>
    <string name="user_not_found">The user with this email was not found</string>
    <string name="new_password_email">A new password has been sent to your email</string>
    <string name="enter_email">Enter email</string>
    <string name="quit_app">Are you sure you want to get out?</string>
    <string name="quit_profile">Are you sure you want to log out of your personal account?</string>
    <string name="time">Time\'s up</string>
    <string name="questio">Question</string>
    <string name="time_test_new">The time for completing the survey is over. Start from the beginning</string>
    <string name="ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="in_result">To the results</string>
    <string name="answer_saved">Your answer is saved</string>
    <string name="quit_test">Are you sure you want to complete the test?</string>
    <string name="fields_required">All fields are required</string>
    <string name="incorrect_email">You have entered an incorrect email</string>
    <string name="successfully_registered">You have successfully registered</string>
    <string name="fail_auth">Authorization error</string>
    <string name="lang">EN</string>
    <string name="Typeback">Вернуться к списку типов</string>
</resources>